BRIAN CHIANG

DETAILS

PHONE

7066199075

EMAIL

kysiric@gmail.com

SKILLS

Data Entry

Customer Service

Product Dispensing

Multitasking

Programming

Adaptability

Inventory Management

LANGUAGES

English

Some Chinese

PROFILE

My have diverse experience in motel management, pharmacy technician, and web development. These are different aspects of my life that has built the me that is today. Knowledgeable in customer service, data entry, product dispensing, booking, and coding are just a few skills I have learned over the years.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Motel Receptionist, Henry Chiang

Augusta

Aug 2008 — Aug 2015

- · I learned how to make a quality experience for the customers.
- · A smile goes a long way even among a customer that may just have a bad day.
- · I helped book customers in and check them out on time.
- If a customer made any requests then it was my job to ensure the request gets completed by the correct department
- · I helped record transactions physically, and online.

Pharmacy Technician, Kroger

Suwanee

Aug 2017 — Oct 2022

- My work obligations include but not limited to, data entry, data analysis, customer service, and product dispensing.
- Patient information and prescriptions have to be inputted accurately.
 Checking for mistakes constantly while also typing at around 80 wpm is standard for my day to day work. If there is an error, knowing how to quickly identify and fix it through procedural checks is common.
- Patients are our priority concern, and must be attended to right away.
 Identifying the patient's concern or need is the first objective before looking into how to resolve it.
- I value my strength to understand things from the customer's standpoint and to show compassion and the will to work with them in resolving their needs.
- It was necessary for me to multitask objectives such as product dispensing while also helping a customer on the phone.
- I also have experience in the customer service industry for 9 years of my life working during pre-college years under my parents.

EDUCATION

Computer Science, Georgia Southern University

Statesboro

May 2015 — Dec 2016

Web Development, Georgia Institute of Technology Boot Camp

Atlanta

Oct 2022 — Present